Your Uncle Barney was always
always a bit of an enigma.
In all the years we
lived in New York,
none of us had ever set
foot in his apartment.
Until one day, one of us did.
It's a pretty good story.
And believe it or not,
alcohol did not play a role.
It all started two weeks
earlier at Lily's housewarming.
Hey, welcome to my new home.
Oh, wow, Lily, this is...
Oh, this is all of it.
Yeah, I know it's small,
but it's got character.
Thank you.
And I am learning Lithuanian
from my neighbors.
They're great.
They're always out there in the hall,
you know,
cooking and gambling and
giving each other haircuts.
It's nice.
Hey, is that a toilet
in your kitchen?
Or a stove in your bathroom?
Oh, that's not just a stove.
That's a stovenkerator:
a combination of a stove,
oven and sink and refrigerator.
Stovenkerator.
Isn't that futuristic?
God, I hope not.
Hey, cool Murphy bed.
Yeah, it's kind of a mess.
I didn't make my bed this morning, so...
Oh!
You know what, I bet sleeping
at this angle is good for you.
For some reason.
I got it.
That was, something, something,
I am going to, something,
you like a, something, donkey.
Huh.
Other cultures.
Hey, let's break out
the fruit basket.
Hey, who ate all the...?
Sync by vNaru
Okay, we have to get Lily out of that
apartment. Her roommate is a raccoon.
I'd offer her my place,
but I've got dogs and she's allergic.
Dogs? I live with her ex-boyfriend. I think
she's a little more allergic to that.
The Fortress of Barnitude?
No way.
Come on. She's desperate.
Hmm, normally a prerequisite
for the women I bring home,
but... pass.
One of you guys is very,
very lucky because I have...
a boom, an extra ticket to the
Alanis Morissette concert. Who's in?
- Absolutely not.
- No.
Damn! I got these tickets,
like, months ago for me and Lily
and now I can't find
anyone to go with me.
This is what I miss
about being in a couple.
I always had someone to
go to concerts with,
or farmer's market,
or brunch.
God, I miss brunch!
Well, I guess you could-- well,
you could try going to brunch alone.
Oh, you don't think I've tried?
Table for one.
One couple?
Um, no, just me.
Really?
For brunch?
You're right. Who am I kidding?
Ooh, The Popover Pantry. That place is
great. Can we go get brunch tomorrow?
Of course, sweetie.
Can I go with you guys?
Really? For brunch?
God, I hate being single!
Okay, I'll take the over
on the Pittsburgh game.
Oh, and P.
to the S., I never got my payout
from Seattle from
two weeks ago.
Yeah. Don't make me call the
gaming commission on you.
I'm sure they'd be very interested
to know what's going on over there.
All right? All right?
Okay, I love you, too, Mom.
Take care.
Hello, Lily.
You've somehow managed to
circumvent my security.
How did you do it?
Ted gave me your spare key.
Spare key, brilliant!
I'm sorry,
but you know I'd only come here
if I had no other choice.
But earlier today, I was getting
ready to go to sleep and...
Sveikas.
That's terrible.
Well, see ya.
Well, can I stay here maybe?
Oh... I'd let you,
but I don't have any room.
You live in a
two-bedroom apartment.
You have one room
just for your suits.
Hey, I'm at a point in my life
where my suits are my family.
Look around you, Lily.
You are in the heart
of bachelor country,
and as a woman,
you are an illegal immigrant here.
Now, you can try to apply for a sex
visa, but that only lasts 12 hours.
14 if you qualify
for multiple entry.
Eww... is something some lame,
judgmental chick would say,
but I say give me
multiple high fives.
Wow, you really are desperate.
I really am.
Okay, you can stay
here for two days.
But I only have one rule.
You can't change anything.
Why would I change anything?
This place is...
...perfect.
Except for the fact that
you don't have a TV.
See that wall?
300-inch flat-screen.
They only sell them in Japan,
but I know a guy.
Had to ship it over in a
tugboat like freakin' King Kong.
It hurts my eyes.
Yeah. That doesn't go away.
- Hey.
- Hey, where have you been?
The Alanis Morissette concert.
By yourself?
No, actually I went with
a friend from law school.
Oh, really? Who's this friend?
Brad.
- Bro, Alanis Morissette rocks!
- Totally!
I can't believe I almost
didn't come tonight.
Let me guess:
You bought the tickets for you and Lily
right before she dumped you.
Yeah, how'd you know?
I just got dumped myself.
What, Kara broke up with you?
I'm sorry, man. That sucks.
Brad, do you like brunch?
You invited him to brunch?
Yeah, I invited him to brunch.
Why, is that weird?
Yes. That's why I was all,
"You invited him to brunch?"
Why can't two guys who
are friends go to brunch?
Because brunch is kind of...
Girly.
Girly? Breakfast isn't girly.
Lunch isn't girly.
What makes brunch girly?
I don't know.
There's nothing
girly about a horse.
Nothing girly about a horn,
but put them together
and you get a unicorn.
I don't care what
either of you say,
I am going to The
Popover Pantry with Brad.
We're here. We're hungry.
Get used to it, brunch.
- Hmm... smells delicious.
- Thank you.
There was no food in the fridge,
so I picked up...
What are you doing?
Lily, what was the
first rule again?
Don't change anything.
And what was the second rule?
- There was no second rule.
- Exactly!
There was only one
rule and you broke it.
I bought groceries.
That counts as changing something?
Lily, if I wanted a
fridge full of groceries,
or fresh coffee in the morning,
I'd be in a relationship.
But I don't want to
be in a relationship.
That's why I make it crystal-clear to
every girl that walks through that door
that this is not a place
to leave a toothbrush.
This is not a place to
leave a contact lens case.
This is a place to leave.
Come on, I'll give you a tour.
Uh, no flash
photography, please.
Bienvenido to the bedroom.
Dig this: king-sized bed,
full-sized blanket, one pillow.
Everything about this bed says,
"our work here is done."
Next we say "bienvenue"
to the bathroom.
What, only one towel?
What, no hairdryer?
You know where I keep that stuff?
Your place. Beat it.
And the coup de grace...
Yeah, that's right.
Patent-pending.
And wilkommen to the hallway.
While guys like Ted and
Marshall may hide their porn...
Marshall doesn't have porn.
Aww, that's sweet.
While guys like Ted and
Marshall may hide their porn,
I had mine...
professionally lit.
Girls see this, they can't
get out of here fast enough.
And if that doesn't
drive them away,
there's always your
life-sized storm-trooper.
No, that's just awesome.
So you see,
whenever a girl wakes up here,
I never have to tell her to go
build her nest somewhere else.
My apartment does it for me.
God, I love brunch.
Oh, damn...
the zucchini bread
is "ridonculous."
This isn't weird, right?
I sort of thought it might be,
but it totally isn't.
And B-T-dub, you totally did
not oversell the eggs Benny.
Right? Right?
I mean, why can't two single bros go out
and rock brunch Sunday morning-style?
Exactly. Thank you,
that's exactly what I've been saying.
This must be destiny.
What are you talking about?
I have two tickets for
Mamma Mia Friday night.
You like Abba, right?
What am I saying? Who doesn't?
Anyway, I was gonna take Kara,
but now it's all you and me.
We're gonna do Broadway, bro style.
What do you say?
Yeah!
Hey. Did the cold wake you?
No, I've just been
watching you sleep.
Oh, did you try and take a shower?
I'm sorry, I only have one clean towel.
I don't buy into the myth that
we need to shower every day.
Okay.
I'd offer you some coffee, but I don't
have any, so you're gonna have to...
I'm boycotting coffee.
You may as well drink the tears
of a Colombian peasant farmer.
God, I love this place.
Good thing I don't have a job
because I could
stay here all day.
I think I left something
on the bookshelf.
Whoops. Oh, no, oh, look.
Oh, I'm disgusting.
Wow, you're open
about your sexuality
and that's one of the
reasons I love you.
Did I just say that?
Oh, well, cat's out of the bag.
I love you.
Whoa, uh... Okay, beep, beep.
Backing up, um...
Hi, Barney. Oh...
Oh, my God. Are you married?
Is this your wife?
What? No.
Yes!
- Yes?
- Yes.
You son of a bitch!
I can't believe I let
you enter my sacred temple.
Come on, baby. Please, no.
Oh, you don't understand.
What have I done? This is the worst.
How could you...?
You're not going anywhere.
Wow, that was close.
That hippie chick
wouldn't leave.
She was ready to squat here.
Well, she'd have to with your
spring-loaded toilet seat, wouldn't she?
She was freakishly immune to
everything in my apartment...
except you.
You're better than porn.
Thank you.
How would you like to
extend your stay here?
All you'd have to do is
pretend to be my wife,
and scare off the
occasional one-night stand.
I know, I know. You've got your ethics.
You've got your principles...
I'll do it.
Really?
Barney, you've clearly got
some serious mother issues
that have left you the emotional
equivalent of a scavenging sewer rat.
But, in my other apartment,
I would be living
with an actual scavenging sewer rat,
so you win.
I'll take it.
- Mamma Mia?
- Mamma Mia.
You know what? It's supposed
to be a great musical, okay?
It won all sorts of
Tonys and stuff.
No, totally. It sounds like a really,
really fun, exciting, third date.
Ooh, third date.
You know what that means.
It is not a date, okay.
It's just two bros taking
in a Broadway show.
You bros going to get
dinner beforehand?
We might grab a steak, yeah.
Where at?
Cafe L'Amour.
Brad says the food is
really good there, okay.
Sounds like Brad's got
quite the night planned out.
You better bring your "A" game.
That means no granny panties.
All right, you know what?
You two are just threatened
because I'm a single guy moving
in on your couples' turf.
Well, guess what?
It's my territory now.
I'm peeing all over brunches,
fancy dinners and musicals.
That's right;
Brad and I are taking back Broadway.
What are you going to wear?
I was thinking like this
collared shirt and these pin...
Oh, you know what? Shut up.
Can you pass the
Arts and Leisure?
I just did.
Honey, I'm...
Barney, what the hell
is going on here?
Lily, I can explain...
How could you? In our own home?
You bastard!
- I'm so sorry. I didn't know he had...
- Just get out.
This is what I get after I worked
as a stripper for four years
to put you through
medical school?
I got breast implants for you.
I... I was just about
to turn on the tears.
Brava.
That was incredible.
And that slap was genius.
You did not hold back.
Yeah, that I just
always wanted to do.
Fair enough.
I have to say,
it's kind of nice having food
around here for a change.
You know...
nah, never mind.
What?
You're my wife.
You can tell me anything.
Well, if you really
wanted to sell this ruse,
we should try to make this
place a little more...
you know, homey.
Like-like a woman would
actually live here.
What did you have in mind?
♪ Bones, bones,
brittle little bones ♪
♪ It's not the milk you seek ♪
♪ It's the sun you need ♪
♪ Sugar dumpling, muffin baby ♪
♪ This world is going crazy ♪
♪ Do do do do ♪
♪ Do do do do do ♪
Hey, you're home.
I didn't think we'd be seeing
you until tomorrow morning.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
It wasn't a date.
Okay, it was a date
and it got way weird.
Oh, you really don't
have to do that.
No, I insist. You're my guest.
Thanks, Brad.
Bro,
you got some chocolate
on your chin.
Still there.
I'll get that bad boy.
Whoa.
Well, it could have been worse.
It could have
fallen in your lap.
It gets worse.
No, I-I can do it, Brad.
Okay, thank you.
So anyway, ah,
it's this Saturday.
Do you want to come?
You want me to go to
a wedding with you?
Okay, that's not too bad.
Two single guys on the prowl.
It'll be like Wedding Crashers.
Just keep Brad away
from the bouquet.
It gets worse.
It gets better.
The foliage in Vermont this
time of year is ridonc.
Vermont?
Yeah, the wedding's
at this awesome B&B.
Kara and I used to go there.
Anyway, there is one room left,
and we got it.
Walt Whitman Suite, bro.
You said no, right?
Of course.
I understand.
It's cool.
It's the first time I was
going to see my college friends
since Kara left me.
I just...
I just miss her so much.
I'll go to Vermont with you.
That's great!
You know, uh,
they're registered at Pottery Barn.
I figure we could go
halfsies on a gravy boat.
I'm sorry.
It's not funny anymore.
Damn you, brunch!
This guy's crazy, right?
Look, I don't think he's crazy.
I just think he's suffering from a
severe case of girlfriend withdrawal.
And unfortunately,
you're his nicotine patch.
And now you have to do what every
dysfunctional couple has to do:
break up.
You're right. You're right.
I promised Brad
I would go to the wedding with him,
and then that is it.
Good man.
Oh, I think we made
the right decision
going for the custom-made
Italian sheets.
Hey, if my bed's going suit up,
it's going to do it right.
Want to give it a whirl?
All right, I'm going to head out,
hit the bars.
What are you going
to do tonight?
Oh, I was just going to watch Letterman
but, God this bed is so comfy.
I wish you had a TV in here.
Okay, seriously,
what do you do for a living?
Please.
I thought you were going out.
Eh.
After the monologue.
The next morning,
as the sun rose over Manhattan,
your Uncle Marshall headed
over to Brad's apartment
to leave for the
wedding in Vermont.
But when he got there...
No.
No...
No!
No.
Ted.
Um, Brad got me flowers.
Hold on.
Brad got him flowers.
I'm sorry.
It just got funny again.
- Oh, hey...
- No, Brad, uh, I don't want to hear it.
I do like you. And calla lilies
are my favorite flower.
I don't know how you knew that.
I guess you just get me,
but this is not cool, man.
I can't believe that you would...
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey.
- Hey, Marshall.
- Hi, Kara.
So you guys, are like,
back together now?
Yeah. Happened last night.
Uh, I'm sorry, bro.
- I should have called you.
- Yeah, you should have.
- Well, I didn't mean to hurt...
- Don't, Brad.
Just don't.
♪ There was something ♪
♪ in the air that night ♪
♪ The stars went bright ♪
Oh, what was with him?
I don't know.
I think he's in love with me.
♪ Fernando ♪
I can't believe we just...
you and I...
- what have we done?
- Nothing.
Nothing happened.
We-we just went to sleep.
Just went to sleep? I don't sleep
in the same bed as a woman
and not make a move.
How could... You.
You spooned me against my will.
Hey, it takes two to cuddle.
We...
We redecorated my place.
We stayed in on a Friday
night to watch Letterman,
and then slept together
and didn't have sex?
Oh, my God,
we're in a relationship.
That's what you think
a relationship is?
You were supposed
to be the vaccine,
but you gave me the disease.
You gotta go.
Barney.
I don't think you're mad at me.
You're mad at yourself.
You let down your guard,
and let someone into your life,
and-and it actually felt okay.
And that terrifies you.
Uh-huh. You gotta go.
Hey, you can't just kick me out!
I put a lot of work into this place,
and I've grown accustomed to
a certain standard of living.
A certain standard of living?
You didn't pay a single...
And so Mr. and Mrs. Stinson,
after two weeks of marriage,
decided to call it quits.
Fortunately, they
reached a settlement.
And that's the story of how Aunt
Lily furnished her apartment.
Marshall ran into Brad
again some time later.
Oh, my God, it's Brad.
Laugh like I said
something really funny.
Right, right.
Hey, Marshall.
Oh, hey, hey, how's it going?
It's good.
- Hey, I'm, uh...
- Yeah, I know who you are.
Well, I got to go.
I got this thing.
Yeah, me too,
but more important.
So, I guess I'll
see you around.
Sure. Sure.
Even if you don't believe it,
tell me he looks fat.
Totally looks fat.