Kids, as you know, Christmas is a
time you spend with your family.
So in December of 2006,
I had three options.
Spend it with my mom and
her new boyfriend Clint,
spend it with my dad and his
new girlfriend micro-brewing,
or head down to Staten
Island to spend it
with my super religious
cousin Stacy and her family.
So I opted for
none of the above
and decided to spend
Christmas 2006 in Manhattan...
celebrating with
my other family.
Okay, I have one last paper
due at 5:00 p.m. today,
so until then,
I will be at the law library at school,
but I'm not to be
disturbed for any reason.
Dude, open your eyes.
You're going to hurt yourself.
No, no. Christmas Eve winter
wonderland is my reward
for finishing my paper.
Baby, do I smell your
Sinfully Cinnamon Cookies?
Yes.
Damn me and my
heightened other senses.
Must be strong.
Okay, I'll be back
here at 5:00.
Save me at least 20 cookies
and do not clean the bowl.
Was that a reindeer?
I don't want to know!
Hey, look.
Our old answering machine.
Oh, yeah. After you left,
we, uh, we unplugged it
because it reminded Marshall of how
you used to, you know, leave messages.
But hey,
you guys are back together.
I say we're plugging
it back in.
It's good to have you back.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, look,
there's still some messages on here.
Hey Ted,
it's Dad calling to check in.
I'm going fishing this
weekend with my friend Clint,
so if I don't hear from you beforehand,
I'll talk to you next week.
Yes, same Clint.
Hey, Marshall. Are you lying on the
couch right now moping about Lily?
You are, aren't you?
Well, stop it.
She's not worth it.
You gotta get over that Grinch.
But I didn't say "Grinch."
I said a bad word.
A very, very bad word.
Oh, fudge.
But I didn't say fudge.
Sync by vNaru
I'm... a what?
I-- That was Barney,
that was Barney.
- That was you, Ted.
- That was Marshall.
Marshall left a
message for Marshall?
You know, it may have been me,
but it was so long ago.
Man, that machine,
it really garbles your voice.
You know, it almost
made it sound like I said...
Why would you call me that?
It was a fair question.
Marshall's breakup with Lily had
sent him into a deep depression
and nothing could
get him out of it.
Until one day...
She was perfect.
I lost the perfect woman.
I should have knocked her
up when I had the chance.
Okay. That's it.
You're never going to get over her until
you stop putting her on a pedestal.
So no more ice cream until you tell
me one thing that's wrong with Lily.
There's only one of her?
Okay.
She called off your wedding
and dumped you to be a
painter in San Francisco.
What do you call that?
Fiercely independent?
Brave?
I guess it was a
little selfish.
There you go.
And in almost no time,
that spark turned into a roaring fire.
Yeah. No, you're right.
Lily would laugh at anything.
She'd give it up for a bad pun.
I'm telling you,
she's a laugh slut.
Remember that time we
heard her laughing
and we thought she was
watching Weekend At Bernie's,
but it turned out she was
watching Weekend At Bernie's 2?
And her art?
"I'm Lily, I'm an artist."
She doesn't even own a beret.
Yeah, and if she's
such a great "artist,"
why does she suck
at Pictionary?
Who draws a ninja star like a
Star of David? Right, right?
Yeah!
- Another round!
- Yeah!
I was trying to help him.
I'm his best friend.
That's the best friend's job.
The best friend's job is
to call me that word?
Yeah.
Oh, Ted.
Oh, Teddy boy.
Why is this such a big deal?
It's just a word.
We use lots of words,
every day.
It shouldn't be any different
than any other word.
Then why don't you say it now?
Grinch.
You timed that didn't you?
Perfectly.
Well, at least you apologized.
You apologized, didn't you?
Oh, yeah.
"I'm sorry" were the first
words out of my mouth.
I'm sorry,
but I am not apologizing.
I was just trying to put
the guy back together.
You smashed him to pieces.
Are you seriously not going to
apologize for leaving that message?
- No!
- Why not?
Because, Lily, this summer,
you were kind of a Grinch.
- Oooh.
Oh, you'll be sorry, Ted Mosby.
Ted Vivian Mosby!
That's not my middle name.
You kiss your mother
with that mouth?
Like you've never
said that word.
I don't kiss your
mother with my mouth.
Yet.
Are you sick?
Is it sick to find maturity
and experience sexy?
No, I meant do you have a cold?
I'm fine.
I'm fine. My nose
is just overflowing with awesome
and I had to get
some of it out.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
the holidays are a time
when people are
lonely and desperate.
It's the most wonderful
time of the year.
I should go apologize.
It's Christmas Eve.
Yeah. I mean,
slamming doors and screaming curses?
If I wanted that, I would
have gone home for the holidays.
I don't see any
mistletoe, but...
Oh! Oh, God!
Uh... "Bless you"
would have been nice.
- You're sick.
- I'm not sick.
- You know what? I am sick.
Sick of you telling me I'm sick.
What up?
Ahh... Three flights of stairs,
not a drop spilled.
Hey, buddy.
You sure this is gonna work?
Yeah, this is our thing.
In college, whenever I wanted to make
up with her, I'd buy her a beer.
- Cute, right?
- Totally.
Plus free mug.
Okay, come on.
Usually that would've
done the trick,
but it turned out this was a problem
not even alcohol could solve.
Actually the beer
helped a little.
She took the decorations.
She took the decorations!
What a Grinch!
That time I did say "Grinch."
All right.
I guess I have to
call her, right?
Lily's cell phone.
She'll listen to
reason-- right?
Oh, hey, Billy.
Actually, funny thing--
the voice dial got you.
I was trying to call...
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, the holidays are a rough
time for everyone, Billy.
Okay, yeah,
dinner next Wednesday.
Okay.
Damn voice dial.
Barney! What the
hell are you doing?
Get in here, it's freezing outside.
Are you insane?
Hey, blame Lily and her oppressive
"no cigars in the apartment rule."
God, it's like Marshall's
marrying the Taliban.
High five.
Eww. No.
You have to go home
and get to bed.
Oh, Robin, my simple friend
from the untamed north,
let me tell you about a little
thing I like to call mind over body.
You see,
whenever I start feeling sick,
I just stop being sick
and be awesome instead.
True story.
Yeah, in two minutes,
I'm going to pound a sixer
of Red Bull, hop in a cab,
play a couple of
hours of laser tag,
maybe get a spray-on tan.
It's gonna be legen...
Wait for it...
Lily!
Merry Christmas, assface.
Um, Lily?
Where are the Christmas decorations?
At my apartment.
You want to bring them back so we can
celebrate Christmas together-- please?
Ted, do you know
what I would do
if one of my kindergartners
used that kind of language?
I would be on the phone
with their parents.
Yeah, I'm not a kindergartner.
Exactly. You know
what that word means.
You know that calling people
names is mean and hurtful...
assface.
Lily, if you don't bring that
stuff back right now, we...
She hung up.
She's just mad.
She'll cool down.
Lily...
Don't forget to take the
cookies out of the oven...
assface!
Damn it!
I could be in Cleveland right now
making peppermint lager with my dad.
Where are you going?
Marshall gets home
in three hours.
He's gonna show up--
no Lily, no winter wonderland.
I gotta get up to the Bronx.
...dary.
Hey, dude,
how's the paper going?
Screw the paper, how's the winter
wonderland? Is it magical?
Oh... so magical.
When you walk through the door,
does it feel like
you've been slapped in
the face by Christmas?
Sure does. Look, I gotta go.
Come on, man, describe it!
Tell me about the decorations.
Is Rudolph there?
He is, isn't he?
Hi, Rudolph!
Ah, yeah, but, you know...
decorations, is that really
what Christmas is about?
Hell, yeah!
What else would it be about?
Uh, try the birth of Christ.
You know, Christmas--
Christ Mas,
which means "More Christ"
to our Spanish friends.
Yeah, well,
all I know is walking in that door
and seeing the winter wonderland
and seeing Lily and all you guys,
just... I can't wait.
Right. I gotta go.
Right. Okay.
Oh, wait. Ted, Ted, Ted, Ted.
One more thing.
How about the cookies?
Are they delicious?
You know, honestly,
they taste a little store-bought.
Oh! I got another call.
Well, tell Lily I love her.
Right.
- Hello?
- Ted Evelyn Mosby!
Oh. Uh, hey, Mom.
Merry Christmas.
I just got the most
disturbing call from Lily.
How could you use
such a horrible word?
Oh, God, she called you?
Are you acting out
because of the divorce?
Is-is this all about Clint?
No, Mom,
why would it be about Clint?
Hey, buddy, it's Clint.
How you doing, champ?
Hey, Clint. Listen, um,
I don't really have time to...
Hey, hey, no, no, no. Ted, Ted.
You don't know this yet,
but you and I are going
to be great friends.
Now, the Native Americans
have this ritual...
This is a low moment
for the Barnacle.
I should be off playing
laser tag right now,
but instead...
Don't look at me. I'm hideous.
You just look like
a regular guy.
Exactly.
I'm a Ted.
I'm wearing elastic-waist fleece pants.
And isn't it more comfy?
Yes.
Come on,
you need eat something.
Too weak... to hold... bowl.
Fine, I'll feed you.
Ouchie in my mouth!
I don't want it.
I want ice cream.
No, you're not having ice cream
for dinner just 'cause you're sick.
- But my throat hurts.
- No.
I hate you!
Don't leave me.
Who is it?
Pizza delivery.
Whoa.
Hey, you tricked me.
You really thought I was
the pizza delivery guy?
No, I knew it was you.
I just thought you'd at
least bring a pizza.
Yeah, well,
I brought a beer,
but I gave it to a homeless guy.
All right, he took it from me.
Now, will you please come home?
No, I'm not spending
Christmas with you.
Okay, I'm sorry for
calling you a...
that word,
over the summer,
and for saying it again today.
And for thinking it a lot
on the subway ride over.
I had no right to say that. It was
hurtful and immature and I'm sorry.
Oh, shut up.
You think I don't know your fake
apologies by now, Ted Mosby? Huh?
You're clearly still mad at me.
- I'm not mad at you.
- Yes, you are.
I am not mad at you, Lily.
Now, can we please just...
I've apologized to Marshall
and he's forgiven me
and we've moved passed it.
Why can't you?
Because you never
apologized to me.
Marshall's not the only
one you walked out on.
You leave for three months,
you don't even call.
Come on, Lily,
we're supposed to be friends!
Yeah, some friend,
you called me a Grinch.
- You were a Grinch!
- How can you...
Grinchy, Grinch, Grinch,
Grinch, Grinch, Grinch, Grinch.
Happy?
Now, you've pissed off
the big guy upstairs.
Yeah, I'm sure
God cares if I...
You use that language again
and I'll turn off your water!
That's my super.
He lives above me.
Great. Thanks to
your filthy mouth,
now I'm going to have
Christmas alone in the dark.
Fine. I don't want
to ruin Christmas.
You can have the apartment.
Don't worry about seeing me there
I'll be in Staten Island
with my cousin Stacy.
Just....
Ow.
Merry Christmas.
You're spending Christmas
Eve with your family?
Baby, that sucks. I'm so sorry.
Uh, they're fine. They're just...
they're a little weird.
You know they don't believe
in gifts or Christmas trees.
And they think Santa's
how Satan spells his name
when he wants to trick us.
Well, do you want
me to go with you?
Was that a sincere offer?
First tell me your answer.
Stay there. Save yourself.
We'll spend all day
together tomorrow.
Okay.
Oh, how's Barney feeling?
You mean the whiney
bottomless pit of neediness?
He was bugging me, so I spiked
his echinacea tea with codeine.
You're gonna be a great mom.
Holy crap, the magical
Christmas season is upon us.
And thank God we don't
pay for utilities.
Merry Christmas!
What's in the box?
Only the best present
for the best girl ever.
It took me all day
to track it down.
I thought you were
writing a paper.
Ah, naw, I blew that off.
I'll get an extension.
School's not important.
What is that pitter
patter on the roof?
Could it be the sound of
an awesome Christmas story
about to come down the chimney?
Why, yes, it is.
'Twas the day
before Christmas...
It was supposed to arrive,
like, five days ago,
but then it got
lost and rerouted.
I checked two other branches,
finally they told me it was here.
Yeah, all I needed to know
was the tracking number.
Looks like it's headed out to our
regional branch in Poughkeepsie.
What?
No, no, no, no,
I need that package today.
Listen, the truck already
left five minutes ago,
so unless you want
to run after it...
Stop! Stop!
Stop, please, stop.
Stop. Stop the truck.
I need a package on your truck.
Can I please take a look in back?
Sure. But I gotta keep
driving my route.
I'm running behind.
My bad.
I'm okay.
Hey, man, thanks for helping me
make my fiancée's Christmas.
No problem.
Too bad I can't deliver all these
packages by the end of the day.
Wait, so some people aren't going to
get their gifts in time for Christmas?
Sadly, no.
♪ They call me back door Santa ♪
♪ I make my runs ♪
♪ about the break of day ♪
♪ They call me back door Santa ♪
♪ I make my runs ♪
♪ about the break of day ♪
♪ Oh, ho, ho ♪
♪ I make all ♪
♪ the little girls happy... ♪
We delivered every single
package on that truck.
But I still have one
package left to give.
Yeah, I did.
Merry Christmas.
- Open it, Baby.
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
An Easy Bake Oven!
I've wanted one of these ever
since I was a little girl.
In this exact model.
I never told you that.
How did you know?
It's our first Christmas
since we got back together.
I want to get her
something really special.
So I'm getting her a jukebox.
Wow, that's a great gift.
Not really.
It's this big and it dispenses gum.
Oh, man, I know
something you could get her
that would blow her mind.
Ready?
Eight years ago...
When I was a kid,
all I wanted was an Easy Bake Oven.
I begged and I begged,
but all I got was a stupid Lego set
because my feminist mom
didn't want me conforming to
traditional gender roles.
Easy Bake Oven--
that's what I'm going to call my van.
Dude... how was the concert?
I couldn't find the outside.
I can't believe Ted remembered
after all these years.
Yeah, and after all that weed.
Where is he anyway?
Staten Island.
Why?
Okay, don't tell your mom,
but I got you guys some presents.
Like the gift
of God's love?
No, dude, real presents.
Uncle Ted got us presents!
That's okay, Ted,
we'll just give them to charity.
Yay!
Uh, not you, Charity.
I meant the less fortunate.
Ted, how would you like
to say grace tonight?
Uh, you know what,
why don't you say it.
I really wouldn't
know what to say.
Why don't you recite your
favorite passage of scripture.
That's a great idea, Charity.
But, really, I don't know.
I mean how do you choose
your favorite passage?
It's the Bible; there's so many...
great ones...
That one from Pulp
Fiction's pretty cool.
Ooh, I'll get it.
Charity, I'm tapping you in.
Dear, Father,
thank you for this day,
and thank you for bringing
this family together.
Amen.
Who is it, Ted?
Uh, it's...
it's just, um, carolers.
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night... ♪
I came here to apologize.
I'm so sorry, Ted.
I accept. Give me the beer.
Oh, oh,
it is so good to see you guys.
Are you coming home?
Totally.
But first, Lily,
I owe you an apology.
Oh, for the love of God,
are you as sick of apologies as I am?
Yes!
Can we just skip the apology and
go straight to the forgiving?
Yes.
And I promise, I will never ever
call you a... you know, again.
That's okay.
I was kind of a Grinch.
What's a Grinch?
Nothing. It's something
you shouldn't say.
Mom, what's a Grinch?
Grinch, Grinch, Grinch...
Merry Christmas, everybody.
Run, run.
Merry Christmas, Marshall.