Kids, there's nothing
more wonderful
than New York City
in the winter...
except the view of New
York City in the winter
through your apartment window.
In the winter of 2006,
Marshall, Lily, Robin and I
were all deep in couple
hibernation mode.
Sadly, this left Uncle
Barney out in the cold.
Okay. All-night rave,
abandoned tire
factory in Newark.
We're on the list. Who's in?
- Nope.
- No.
Private jet. Teeterboro Airport,
skinny-skydiving. Who's in?
- Nope.
- No, thanks.
One beer. Bar, downstairs,
15 second walk. Who's in?
Shh... Lily went sleepy-bye.
It got so bad,
Barney tried to be his own wingman.
Hi. Have you met me?
Finally, he decided to
bring in reinforcements.
- No.
Yes. And do you know why?
Hang on to your bedsores,
grandparents from Willy Wonka,
because guess who's on his way
up to this apartment right now?
My... wait for it...
brother, James. React.
- Hey!
- You have a brother?
- Yeah.
He's the "awesome-est," most best
"looking-est," greatest guy ever.
He's exactly like Barney.
That's what I just said.
Well, Barney and his brother
aren't exactly alike.
James is gay.
Really? I never in
a million years
would I picture you with a gay brother,
that's awesome.
Yeah. I just wanted
you to have a heads up,
so you don't act all
surprised when he gets here.
Here he is.
What up, New York.
Thanks for the heads up.
How in God's name did it never come up
that Barney has a gay, black brother?
Is he black?
I guess I'm the kind of person that
focuses on who people are on the inside
rather than the
color of their skin.
I'm kidding,
I just wanted to see your face.
Yeah, so now the
wedding's back on.
Anyway, James,
how have you been?
Awesome, as per "yoozh."
I just went
skinny-skydiving. Legendary.
And my laser tag team,
just made it to regional finals.
"Legendarier."
And by now you've
noticed the suit--
go 'head, touch it.
Handcrafted by
Pietro Dellacamera,
Milan's famous
101-year-old tailor
who upon completing
the very last stitch
in this suit dropped dead,
which is ironic because that
is how gorgeous I look in it.
C'mon.
Gimme five.
Is "gimme five" back?
Oh, yeah.
I put it in my blog this morning.
Guys, "gimme five" is back!
Oh, James,
this is my girlfriend, Robin.
- Hey. It's so nice to meet you.
- You, too.
So, I have to ask,
there's a story here.
Please.
The truth is,
Barney and James got a lot of...
different explanations from
their mom over the years.
Well, boys, you look different
because when I was
pregnant with you,
I only ate vanilla ice cream.
And when I was
pregnant with you,
can you guess what kind
of ice cream I ate?
- Coffee?
- No, James,
I ate chocolate ice cream.
But I did drink tons of coffee when
I was pregnant with both of you.
Can't smoke without my coffee.
I don't know, boys,
I guess it's just one of those things.
Stop asking me!
You  know what you two are?
You're little racists!
So what are you guys
gonna do tonight?
I'll tell you what
James is gonna do.
He's gonna do the job
you've been neglecting.
And, as always, he'll do it a
lot better than you ever did.
Ted...
James is my wingman now.
Okay.
Last time James was in town,
Barney got slapped once,
lucky twice, and...
whose penthouse hot
tub did you end up in?
Ah, public figure,
confidentiality agreement.
But I will say this:
way more back hair than any guy
who can afford laser hair
removal should have.
And then there was the time they
scored the brother/sister combo.
It was everything
we ever dreamed of
when watching Donnie and Marie.
She was a little bit country.
He was a little bit
way into black guys.
Yeah, Barney and James together
was a lethal combination.
Since there was never
any crossover in targets,
James was always there for
Barney with the assist.
Whoa. Your scarf...
it is fierce!
Thanks. H & M.
What? I would never know,
'cause it is so hot that my eyes
are melting. Oh, I can't see.
Hey! You know,
speaking of things
that would look good
wrapped around you,
have you met my straight
brother, Barney?
Oh, he is fab--
don't you go nowhere-- "ulous." Okay?
And Barney always
returned the favor.
Help, I don't think
he's breathing.
Does anyone
know mouth-to-mouth?
Oh, my God, I do!
Okay, great.
How 'bout you instead?
Oh, man,
I am so excited that you're here!
It has been forever since
I have been around anyone
even remotely fun.
Uh, yes offense.
You guys are still going
out with us tonight, right?
- No.
- Jammies.
Tonight? It's after 9:00 and...
I have warm soup belly.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Guys...
you are young,
attractive people here
in the greatest city on earth.
There  are boys and girls
in Nobody Cares, Wyoming,
wishing they could be here.
But instead, they are in someone's
basement drinking bad malt liquor,
debating whether or not they're
going to spend their Saturday night
in  the parking lot
of the feed store
or in some other
dude's basement.
You owe it to them to rise up
and shimmy your lazy
asses into something hot,
and you go out there and
you live their dream!
- Can I get a "hell, yeah"?
- Hell, yeah!
- Can I get a "woo-woo"?
- Woo-woo!
Go do it for Wyoming! Yes!
Testify!
So that night,
Barney got his wish.
We all went out.
Daddy's home!
Yeah.
All right, bro.
What do you like?
Guy in super tight black T?
Super tight black guy?
Guy who looks like Mr. T?
Mmm, yes, yes, and...
talk to me after two martinis.
Let's focus on you, my man.
I'm feeling lazy.
How 'bout girl with
the chocolatini?
Oh... boom, back tattoo.
Hero and the pig?
- Let's ride.
- Fo' 'sho.
Damn baby, nice tramp stamp!
- Get off me, you pig!
- Hey! Hey!
Her body art is not an
invitation to grope her,
it's an expression
of her inner self.
I'm sure, in many ways,
she is the dolphin encircled by flowers.
- What? What?
Cool.
Let me know if he
bothers you again.
Thanks. You should stay close...
just in case.
Sure. If it'll make
you feel safer.
I'm Barney.
Now, kids, when you're out at a noisy,
crowded bar,
you can always tell the
difference between the singles
and the couples.
You just have to
look for the signs.
- Break.
- Boiling hot.
Singles stay on their
feet for maneuverability.
- Hey!
- Hi, how are ya?
Have you met my brother?
Oh, hello. Have a drink.
Nice to meet ya.
Couples, exhausted by the
sheer act of leaving the house,
are obsessed with finding
a place to sit down.
There are a lot of
other indicators, too.
From choice of
social lubricant...
...to basic body language.
But the point is,
there are many ways to tell
whether someone
has Single Stamina
or Couples Coma.
I wish I would've
worn sneakers.
I just got finished running
from some fat, hairy guy
who was periscoping out
of his pleather pants.
Permission to come
aboard denied.
I miss my jammies.
I can't believe I
wore a bra for this.
Bras suck.
They're so confining and unnatural.
Yeah, they're like
a boobie zoo.
Well, why don't you take it off
then and let those puppies breathe?
Oh, please go sweat
on someone else.
Poor guy.
Poor guy? Poor my boobs.
Well, it takes a lot of
guts to approach a girl
and you just crushed him.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He looks all broken up inside.
Whatever, you guys have
no idea what it's like
to be on the receiving end.
"Oh, poor me. I'm a pretty girl
and everybody everywhere
wants to buy me drinks
and have sex with me."
Waa.
"Oh, poor me.
I get to order yummy, pink drinks
with chunks of real fruit
that guys secretly like,
but  can't order because
they'll be made fun of."
- Dude.
- They're delicious!
Excuse me. Join me in a shot?
Oh, no thanks. I've had enough.
He's too in shape,
we'd spend all night talking
about his body fat content.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go have a yummy,
pink drink with fruit in it...
because I can.
You know, that was,
like, the third hot guy
that James blew off tonight.
Yeah, he's turning down shots,
he's yawning,
he's whining about his feet.
He's as bad as we are.
He is.
Wait, he's exactly as bad as we are.
You guys don't think that James is...
in a relationship?
No. There's no way.
He's Barney's brother.
Look at that.
He's texting!
Oh, my God!
He is in a couple.
This is gonna kill Barney.
What's gonna kill me?
What's going on?
B-Barney?
Have you noticed anything...
different about James?
No.
I mean, he's glowing from his peel,
if that's what you mean.
We have reason to believe
that James is, uh,
maybe hiding
something from you.
I-I know you're not gonna
like hearing this, but...
Barney...
your brother is...
monogamous.
That's ridiculous!
Just because he's
a little sleepy,
and he hasn't had sex with
anyone in a bathroom stall...
He hasn't had sex with
anyone in a bathroom stall.
And, Barney...
I hate to be the one to
tell you this, but...
he's texting.
No, he... No!
That... is impossible.
Excuse... Excuse... Ex...
Hey, bro.
Don't change the subject.
Let me see your phone.
Why?
I just want to see your phone.
Let me see your phone.
No, it's just a phone.
It's just a phone!
And it's got Internet access,
and it's got a camera on it,
and you can surf the Web
and do the whole thing.
It's so amazing how far
technology has come.
What kind of phone do you have?
I got...
Who is this?
And the answer better be:
"I don't remember his name."
That is Tom.
And he's my fiancé.
Hey.
I don't support this.
Gay marriage?
Not gay marriage-- marriage!
How can you do this?
We  were raised in the same house,
with the same values!
Believe me,
I fought this for a long time.
Come on, it's embarrassing.
Look, this felt unnatural to me,
too, at first.
But I fell in love.
And Tom and I realized
you can't fight love.
Oh, God.
Is that what you two do together?
You sit around the house
and talk about love?
I think... I'm gonna be sick.
Okay, okay, look,
I need you to wrap your
head around this, okay?
Because it is happening.
And I want you to
be my best man.
What? No way.
Well, I'm sorry
you feel that way.
I hope you change your mind.
Two beers, one shot.
Oh, it's a freaking epidemic.
Oh, sweetie!
Did you make that for me?
Yes.
Clam Bake.
Staten Island. Who's in?
Okay, I didn't have high
hopes for that one.
Okay, here's my thing.
If gay guys start
getting married,
then suddenly the whole
world's gonna be doing it.
That's how it works.
They start something,
then six months later,
everyone follows.
Like now everyone
gets manicures.
I don't get manicures.
Okay, then like how...
Like getting your chest waxed.
You get your chest waxed?
You know what I mean!
Gay marriage is going
to cause single life,
as we know it, to die out.
Think of how the American
family will be strengthened.
Barney, I'm sorry you're upset,
but you got to suck it up
and be a man about this.
No.
It's always been me and him together,
being awesome,
while the rest of
you walked two-by-two
onto your ark of
sexless boredom.
Just because James
is getting married
doesn't mean things
are going to change.
Yeah. Like things haven't
changed with you people.
Look, my sister married
a guy I didn't like.
Sandals and socks--
come on, buddy.
But I took her out,
we celebrated.
It was the right thing to do.
You got to support him.
You're right, Ted.
This is a cause
for celebration.
We need to take him out and
celebrate the commitment
he and Tom are about to make.
Yeah. This is where
we're celebrating
the commitment that Tom
and I are about to make?
What? Yeah!
See, that cage represents
your commitment.
Oh, my God. Freedom
has never tasted so delicious.
Hey.
You work out?
I do.
And thank you for noticing.
You're obviously in very
good shape yourself.
Well, I try.
So you want to dance?
You know what?
I'm very flattered, and, objectively,
you're a very attractive man,
but this is actually my fiancée.
I'm sorry.
You know, I saw your drink and I...
No, no, this isn't my drink.
This is hers.
No, it isn't.
Whatever.
How 'bout you?
Oh, I'm straight, too.
But I thank you for your time,
and I appreciate your
interest in my body.
You see that?
Being hit on doesn't
have to be terrible.
I feel flattered,
and everyone left with their dignity.
Hey, I really like
your sweater.
Wow. You actually do,
don't you?
You're not checking out
my boobs or anything.
My name's Gay Ken,
what do you think?
I love this place! Let's dance!
- And not be groped!
- Whoo! Thank you.
- Damn.
- Thank you!
- We're hot.
- Totally.
And then Tom says to the dealer
that the handmade Georgian
clock has a chip on the corner.
Blam, we get that puppy half price.
What up?!
Bam!
Sounds like you really rocked
that arts and crafts fair.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Hey, oh, my God.
This is so liberating,
being able to talk
about this to you.
I cannot wait for
you to meet Tom.
And I cannot wait for you
to meet my good friend...
this guy.
Excuse me, do you know anyone
who would like to buy
my incredibly muscular, fun,
large-handed brother a drink?
Eh, eh, eh, let's focus on you,
Barnaby. Okay.
All right. I spy a group of women
who have let their defenses down
because they are in a gay club.
You see that chick right there?
She looks like she'd fall for
sports agent and football player.
Okay, I'm in.
Which one am I?
Please.
He's very shy, loves tennis and Brazil,
and drops his pants
after three dirty martinis.
Now go, man, go!
I just never thought I'd
see Barney so vulnerable.
Well, I guess no one wants to feel like
they're going through the world alone.
Look at me,
in a yummy sandwich!
Okay, we're actually right in the
middle of something right now, so...
Ooh, I know what I want to be
in the middle of. Thoughts?
God, can't two straight guys
come to a gay dance club,
enjoy some techno and good
conversation without being bothered?
How's it going, guys?
Still enjoying the attentions of men?
That's like the eighth guy
who's hit on us in ten minutes.
It's like, hello,
my eyes are up here.
And  it's never the hot ones.
It's always the losers.
Bums me out!
Looks like the boys
learned their lesson.
Do you totally
miss being hit on?
Oh, totally.
Let's go find a sports bar.
James, James,
since you like arts and crafts,
look at what Charles here
made with cherry stems.
He did it with his tongue.
Yeah.
Barney.
So, Charles, why don't you put
your number in my brother's phone,
and once he's in
a funner mood...
Barney, Barney,
I don't want his number.
I don't want anyone's
number, okay?
I'm getting married.
Wow.
- Best of luck to you both.
- Thank you.
My number's in here.
I'm very discreet.
Okay, okay, excuse me.
Barney, family talk.
Okay, dude,
you have got to stop this, okay?
I know that my getting married is
threatening to your way of life...
Oh, so now it's my way of life?
I thought it was
our way of life.
You've completely
turned your back on it.
Look at you,
not even suited up.
Do you remember why
we suit up, James?
To get laid.
To show people that
we are different
from the millions of T-shirt
and jeans lemmings out there.
The suit shows that we are
a force to be reckoned with,
a two-person army that
plays by its own rules.
But you've taken off the uniform,
you've crossed enemy lines,
and you've abandoned me.
Well, I'm not gonna
let you do that.
It's not too late to back out
of this stupid marriage thing!
You don't have to do this, bro!
- Yes, I do.
- Why?!
Because Tom and I are
gonna have a baby.
What? There's gonna be a baby?
Yes. We're adopting.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna be an uncle?
For the rest of your life.
And that's how Barney
became Uncle Barney.
A year later,
at James's wedding,
Barney could not have
been more proud.
To James and Tom.
May you have a long and
happy life together.
And may I always have the skin
and libido of a much younger man.
- Cheers.
Nice one.
Thanks. I decided to leave
out the hetero college phase.
No one wants to
hear about that.
It was perfect.
You even made Tom's dad cry.
Might have been doing that
because he's a Republican.
Whoa.
It's 9:00.
We should be getting back.
You guys want to split a cab?
Uh, no, I think I'm gonna
stay a little bit longer.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm not tired at all.
All right, well, it's getting late.
Got to get the wife home.
Oh, stop calling me that.
It makes me sound fat.
Ugh, it's a freaking epidemic.
- May I?
- Yeah.
Hey, buddy.
Your parents are married.
Now, listen, you.
Just because you're being
raised by married people
doesn't mean you have to
choose that lifestyle.
High-five.
Luckily, you got me.
In 20 and a half years,
you'll be 21,
and I will be...
Well, I haven't decided
how old I'll be yet.
But we are gonna bro out,
uncle and nephew style.
Stick with me, kid.
I am gonna teach
you how to live.
Great suit, by the way.
Who is the cutest?
I don't get it.
Tom liked my breasts
in tenth grade.
Why doesn't he like them now?
Why?
Rosa, why always be attracted
to the unavailable ones?
Why not accept the fact that
you're a beautiful woman
who is worthy of love?
Are you brave enough
to hear that?
You...